[Home](https://gptonline.ai/) > Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

May 13, 2023

At [**GPTOnline.ai**](https://gptonline.ai/), we take your privacy seriously. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, and protect your personal information when you use our website.

Information We Collect
----------------------

When you use our website, we may collect certain personal information from you, such as your name, email address, and IP address. We may also collect non-personal information, such as your browser type, operating system, and website usage data.

How We Use Your Information
---------------------------

We use your personal information to provide you with the services and information you request and to improve our website and services. We may also use your information to communicate with you about updates, promotions, and other news related to our website.

We do not sell or share your personal information with third parties, except as required by law or as necessary to provide our services to you.

Cookies and Other Technologies
------------------------------

We use cookies and other tracking technologies to improve your website experience and to analyze website usage. Cookies are small files that are placed on your device when you visit our website. They help us remember your preferences and provide a more personalized experience.

You can set your browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, please note that some parts of our website may not function properly if you disable cookies.

Security
--------

We take reasonable measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, disclosure, and use. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is completely secure, so we cannot guarantee absolute security.

Changes to this Privacy Policy
------------------------------

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make significant changes, we will notify you by email or by posting a notice on our website.

Contact Us
----------

If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy or your personal information, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://gptonline.ai/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).
